

wangivy1108@gmail.com

## **User Experience & Interface Designer**

https://ivywang1108.github.io/ivyportfolio/

#### About:

Hello, I am ready to design something amazing! I love to learn from research, and craft meaningful decisions that blend into useful solutions. I feel proud being able to bring helpful products to people and see their smiles.

### **Highlights:**

Software Skills: Figma, Adobe Suite, Sketch, Canva, Unity, HTML + CSS.

Design Skills: Design Thinking, User Research, Rapid Design, User Testing,

Wireframing, Interface Design, Interaction Design, Videography.

Soft Skills: Fast Learning, Rapid Thinking, Task Management, Problem Solving,

Critical Thinking.

Languages: English, Mandarin.

### **Experiences:**

## **UX/UI** Designer - AutoMetrics

September 2021 - March 2022

- Took ownership of the entire design process, redesigned the user interface of a
  product that monitors welding operation quality, made decisions on the core
  features and provided users with brand new user-friendly and reliable
  monitor experience.
- Conducted user research to understand current user pain points, developed new product goals and design directions based on user feedback and did competitive analysis to understand industry trends.
- Created marketing videos and brochures that highlighted the company's core features and main services. Also updated the company's website with new product design following company's brand guideline.

### Graphic/UX Design Volunteer - Build a Biz Kids

February 2021 - April 2022

- Maintained the company brand style, designed multiple-day curricula for facilitators that were easy-to-follow, which later became a template for future courses.
- Worked with a company(YouMoveMe) to redesign their Franchise Opportunity Webpage.
- Worked with another designer to re-design the company founder's personal webpage which became more engaging and organised.

- Designed logo for the company's stock game for kids. Did Sketches, and iterations following company brand style while keeping kids as users in mind.

# **Education:**

Simon Fraser University

Bachelor of Arts - Interactive Arts and Technology

Concentration in Design

September 2015 - December 2020